I was pissed off being broke like I think a lot of people don't realize how good life can be
I mean I don't want to be I don't want to shit on everyone's parade and ruin everyone's mind
but everyone here I talk to people and they're content they're like oh I'm happy with loft
golf I'm like why because there's people who have a whole bunch more than you and I was never content
having a normal life I wanted an exceptional life I didn't want a normal car a normal house
a normal girlfriend I didn't want none of that I was like no no no no there's dudes out here
that have the best why do they deserve the best and I don't deserve the best I really believe that
and this is something I've always had inside me I just didn't understand why I couldn't have the
best stuff even now I don't have the best stuff I ain't got a y'all right you know especially when
it came to women for me I saw the kind of girls that the big jeans were getting I was like I don't
want her I want fucking her I want the Instagram model with five million followers what the fuck
and I had a fight coming up the fight was too far away from money and I needed money today
so sitting there thinking how can I make money what do I have that's worth money like what do
I have that I can even sell depression is this big scary monster that strikes your life out of
nowhere and the only way to fix it is with prescription drugs that is what damages people
absolutely and utterly that's more damaging than my mindset which is threefold really one you have
very little control over anything in this life you can't control the weather you might get hit by a
car when you're out the street you can't control anything one of the only things you have absolute
control over because you don't even have control of your own health near you could have a heart
attack in the next 10 minutes only thing you have control over is your own state of mind that's all
you got it's one of the only few things in the world you can control you can decide and people
say oh you can't decide you can't help it yes you fucking can you can decide whether to be positive
or a negative person that's a decision you must make and if you decide to be a negative person it
does not benefit your life in not one percent that's a decision you've made you've decided
that's self-sabotage bullshit so I don't feel sorry for you but for the majority of people
life is depressing you're working a job you fucking hate you know you you want sex and
the girl won't bang you and you're driving a shitty car like that's a depressing element
so what you're gonna do you're gonna be depressed about it cry about it or you're gonna fix your
mindset to make your own life better there's no secret you'll pretend there's some big secret
to it there's no fucking secret and I grew up broke my mom and dad split up we moved I worked
every day I decided I wanted to be a kickboxer I had no car I ran to work which is about four miles
I'd work 10 hours carrying boxes of ice and a fish stall I'd run to the gym from there about
three miles I'd train three hours I'd run home the six miles and that was it there's no secret
you said the fucking I want to do it you don't and people said oh yeah but you must have got this
luck no luck nothing I went I trained I started making I started winning and that's how I started
to make money now all my money is not from kickboxing I mean I made money with kickboxing I didn't make
money with kickboxing I am now but when you start to make you get contacts you know you start to get
big chunks of disposable income you can invest in you start to meet other important people and it
just goes from there I always knew what I had to do and if you're if you're militant enough about
your goals if you stay on track you're gonna succeed to me I it's really that simple easy path
doesn't exist so you know if you want it if you want to be muscle you go to the fucking gym
what do I do in the gym lift the weights how do I lift them pick them up and put them fucking down man
what the fuck lift look at people around you lift the weights it's not complicated but people are just
I don't know I think a lot of people who are doing that are looking for some kind of self
gratification more than looking for actual results no secret man the secret's absolutely no secret
you know it's up to you to change your life and if you don't want to change it you may have a few
people in your life who care enough to pretend they're going to really change your life for you
but you know no one's going to really drag you across that line you got to get up and get it done
or get up and don't get it done and if you're sitting there thinking you know what I really wanted to
be a fucking ice skater and I'm not an ice skater the answer is you didn't really want it because
you really wanted it you wanted the benefits of being an ice skater without the work of being an
ice skater that's what you wanted well who doesn't want that you know I wish I could be the best ice
skater in the world without doing any fucking work so do you I'm sure everyone does but you know you
either want it or you don't have conversations about money talk about it how are you going to get
what you don't talk about it's it's like you use the gym analogy gee I've never met anybody who is
in fantastic shape and you say how'd you get in fantastic shape and he goes oops don't know bro
oops no absolutely not I went to the gym every day I ate this particular way I had a meal plan
I diet nothing is going to happen on accident yeah you're not going to get it on accident your ship's
not going to come in on accident you have the plan for this my unmatched person cassie coupled with
sheer indefatigability makes me a feared opponent in any realm of human which is my saying it's a
saying from my father but it's basically saying unmatched perspicacity so the ability to always
pay attention perspicacity is perception so unmatched I'm always paying attention to everything all the
time and sheer indefatigability I don't become tired makes me a feared opponent in any realm of
human endeavor so a man who always pays attention and never gives up is a feared opponent no matter
what no matter what you're fighting against nobody else is going to wake up and care more about your
life than you if you won't wake up every day and say I need to get rich
nobody else is going to wake up and say I need to make him rich yeah nobody else is going to do it
for you so if you don't think it nobody else is going to think it which means nobody thinks it
so it's down to you right only you're the person you're the only person on the planet who can think
it and I always knew I never doubted for a second I would be what I am I knew I would be rich I just
knew I would be rich and be free and be able to do and say what I wanted I just knew that I was just
like there's no way that guy in the Ferrari who drove past me is a better person there's no way he's
smart yeah and I was not arrogant because arrogance prevents you from working arrogance makes
because I'll make it arrogance is to people who go my ship will come in later arrogance for people
who watch love island but I'll be rich later that's arrogance most people are very arrogant I was never
arrogant I understood okay I'll start working maybe you're smarter than me fine I'll work it I'll
start working no problem it's good to work main reason people aren't aren't rich there's probably three
primary reasons they're either lazy they're arrogant or they're stupid I think lazy is actually
quite a small contingent because I think a lot of people get out here and they work very hard
to a degree like even if you're a trash man that's still work you're working hard you're just not
making any money and also I think if you could show somebody how to make money a lot of people would
would do it I don't think they're that lazy if you say look press this button for money they're not
no I don't want Kenny Baldwin all right okay they're just lazy to find out how perhaps but once
they know how they'll do it stupid I think is also a very small percentage I think that stupid is a
small percentage because I don't think that IQ in fact it's been proven IQ has nothing to do with
how successful you are very rich people very smart people are broke very dumb people are rich how do I
become rich stop chatting shit think of all the hours you wasted watching tv you don't play a video game
ever again and start concentrating on making money if you enjoy making money it's all you're going to
end up doing anyway it hasn't got to be a job all I ever cared about was making money it's all I ever
enjoyed so of course that's all I did and now oops I'm loaded the reason the reason everyone's offended
by what I say is because it points out their own security I know that every man every single human
has a biological imperative to reproduce every single man has a biological imperative to find people
every single man has a biological imperative to want to feel important the easiest way to be happy
as a man is to feel respected if you go places and men and other people show you respect as a man
you feel happy as a man you can't be happy as a man if you're not respected as a man so how do you get
how do you get respected will you pull up in a lambo you have 20 mil on the bank and you've got three
women now that you're respected the fuck so this is the thing the basic tenet if someone asked me to
define masculinity I would define it as um feeling a certain way and doing something and doing the
opposite or ignoring how you feel it doesn't matter how I feel about the gym it doesn't matter if I feel
like going to work none of that's important I do what I'm supposed to do the part the point of being
a man is ignoring how you feel and doing your duty having duty having honor and performing regardless
of how you feel that's the whole point of being a man in the first place so that's the first thing
about it and that's why how you feel isn't that important like people always talk to me about
happiness and I say you spend all your time measuring your happiness if you're I wake up
and I'm a bit pissed off but I still go to the gym I still go to work I still do what I got to do
it doesn't really affect my day it doesn't I don't really cross my mind how I feel doesn't have any
impact how I really live my life and I think that this stoicism is something that a lot of men are
starting to lack nowadays because they're taught they need to give in to their emotions and feel their
emotions what's actually my bigger point about all of this is this who said we're supposed to be
happy who come along and said that that's the rule we're not supposed to be happy you're supposed
to be miserable and that's what drives you to do things that's what this whole conquest is about
so if you were happy without any achievement then we wouldn't have cities and the pyramids and none
of this shit the whole reason the human the human society exists because we were annoyed having less
than we had so this is the normal natural state of man and you need to just get over it I haven't got
time for people to sit there and cry about being unhappy happiness is on top of a mountain so
you don't find it then you don't deserve happiness you're gonna make it happy go get it you don't
want to get it so you don't want to get it and stay miserable
you